hey everyone welcome back to our Channel
I am back with another interesting topic
in the Tosca automation playlist
in this particular session I am going to
show you how you can transfer your
execution results from your execution
list to an Excel sheet now this could be
useful if you have been reporting your
automation results in an Excel format
and if you want to transfer all your
results from your execution list to an
Excel sheet you can do that easily with
Tosca so let me show you how you can do
this
now once you are in your execution list
then you go and open one of your
executions for example this demo webshop
okay so we have got this one execution
which has been done and which was failed
right now if we want to transfer this
into a particular Excel sheet for
reporting purpose then we need to select
all the different
execution folders and execution lists
right and the execution entries and then
right click on that
and then copy table to clipboard okay or
you can also press Ctrl shift and C
after this go to any particular folder
which is your reporting folder there
create an Excel sheet like I have
created for execution results
now open this
and then on the cell just go ahead and
press Ctrl V
and you will see all your execution
results will be pasted into this
particular Excel sheet in the same way
like you have copied it from your
execution less
now whatever columns you have added in
your execution lists will be displayed
here if you have more columns it will
also be displayed here or if you have
less columns then it will display
accordingly now whatever hierarchy we
chose okay so all the folders and all
the execution lists are also showed in
the same hierarchy so you can include as
much details as you want like the
columns or the hierarchy and whatever
other details you want to include you
can just copy the table to the clipboard
and then come to Excel and then paste it
you can also then modify some of the
details like what are these column names
what are the representing right or any
other formatting you want to do at an
Excel level or before you send this
results uh to your stakeholders
so this is a very uh small feature which
is available uh in the execution lists
right so where you can transfer your
results to a particular Excel sheet
which you have been using for reporting
and you can continue to report in the
Excel format
that's all for this particular video if
you have any questions then please leave
it in the comments if you like this
video then please subscribe to our
Channel
thanks for watching and I will see you
in the next video